Lexi Mind is an AI based search engine
that seamlessly integrates Elasticsearch,
Python and React to provide quick and
efficient search results with a feature
to chat about your data.
When you search for something, you
receive search results that match not
only in text but also semantically thanks
to AI. Additionally, you can get a
quick answer about your search directly
from your data. If you wish to delve
deeper into the AI answer, you can engage
in a follow up conversation as well.
Lexi Mind enables you to engage in
conversations about your document with
AI. With the Doc Chat feature, you
can upload your documents and wait for
them to be processed before initiating a
conversation. After the processing is
complete, you can ask questions regarding
the uploaded documents and receive prompt
answers. Compete with page references.
The analyzer feature allows you to upload
a spreadsheet and conduct analysis will
generate conversations based on it.
You can ask it to create lists,
tables or plots the data as well,
as demonstrated in the video.
Ultimately, you can obtain a
presentation of your entire conversation.